



🛮 +380935374841 | 🔀 ashanaakh@gmail.com | 🔏 shanaakh.pro | 🖸 shal | 🛅 ashanaakh

"With hard work and effort, you can achieve anything."

Summary

Currently Lead Golang Engineer at OpenWare. Two years of experience specializing in the backend, concurrency and microservices. Interested in devising a better problem-solving method for challenging tasks, and learning new technologies and tools. I like Go, MacOS, Blockchain, Cloud technologies, but for me - life is also about active lifestyle and travelling.

Skill Highlights

Programming Languages Golang, Ruby, Python, C++

Microservices Docker, Kubernetes Cloud Terraform, AWS, GCP Languages English, Russian, Ukrainian

Education

Taras Shevchenko National University of Kyiv

Kyiv, Ukraine

2015 - 2019

• My GPA is 4.39/5

Program Committees

B.S. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING

Team Member, Google Hash Code Hackathon **Opensource Initiative Winner**, Websummit 2018

Kyiv, Ukraine

Lisbon, Portugal

Experience

OpenWare Kyiv, Ukraine Dec. 2018 - PRESENT

LEAD GOLANG ENGINEER

• Writing idiomatic and resillient Go code

- Software architecture construction and designing
- Specifications and requirements development
- · Code review
- High loaded software development
- Closely coached and mentored new project member

OpenCars Kyiv, Ukraine Jan. 2019 - PRESENT

FOUNDER & GOLANG ENGINEER

- Software designing and implementation
- Telegram bot management
- Specifications development
- Deployment automation

Helios Technologies DEVOPS & GOLANG ENGINEER Kyiv, Ukraine

Jun. 2017 - PRESENT

- Assembling components using Docker
- DevOps tools development
- CI/CD pipelines implementation
- Managing project on Google Cloud Platform
- Build plugins for CI/CD tools
- Build advanced deployments using Kubernetes
- Development of complicated terraform modules
- Design & Implement in-cluster high-speed workers

Palestine Nights

CO-FOUNDER & FULL STACK ENGINEER

- Software designing and implementation
- Specifications development
- Deployment automation
- · Development of APIs
- DigitalOcean deployment automation

Al Muharrag, Bahrain Sep. 2018 - Dec. 2018

ALI SHANAAKH